No! I don't wanna!
Mommy, wait!
What is it, Saki? If you snack now,
you won't be hungry for dinner.
I don't care! I want ice cream right now!
You do? Well, that's a shame.
Dinner tonight's going to be beef stew.
Huh?
I was planning to make a
yummy, yummy beef stew.
I wanna eat dinner!
Is that so? Then can we save
the ice cream for another time?
Yeah, we can!
Saki, where should we go next week?
The pool!
Episode 8 "A Response and Hot Milk"
Do you have cram school today?
Yes.
It looks like the AC's fixed now.
It sure does. I'm glad
we got it fixed so quickly.
Now my girl should be able
to study at home again.
Oh...
That's right.
Say...
Hmm?
Does Ayase-san dislike people who divert
her from doing what she wants to do?
Um, what do you mean?
Well, for example, planning something
without her input and then asking her to join.
Oh, I see.
Considering her personality, I don't think
she'd appreciate that very much.
She'd want it all to be
aboveboard from start to finish.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Oh? Yuta-kun, are you thinking
of asking Saki on a date?
O-Of course not! Ayase-san is my sister.
I'm just kidding.
Ayase-san just seems like the
type to go a little overboard.
I think you mentioned
something like that before.
That she pushes herself too hard.
Mm-hmm.
She always seems to be on guard.
I wonder if she ever actually
gives herself a break.
And that's why you're thinking about
dragging her out to have some fun?
I wonder if she's that way
because I was always so busy.
It's like she's trying to grow
up as fast as possible.
I wish I could have given Saki a little
more time to be a carefree child.
Yuta-kun.
I'd like to ask a favor.
You can insist if you have to,
but make sure Saki takes a break
every once in a while.
All right. Um, but she might hate me for it.
Don't worry!
If it comes to that, I'll let you in on
what Saki's absolute favorite thing is.
And I can use that to get her to forgive me?
Yes, that's for sure.
What?
Listen, about Narasaka-san and the pool—
I'm not going.
I don't have the time.
All right. That's that, then.
But I changed my mind
and am thinking of going.
So do you think you could give me
Narasaka-san's contact info?
No way.
Huh?
U-Um...
It's bad manners to give out someone's
contact info without their permission.
Oh... That's true.
I'll try asking Maaya.
I'll let you know when I get an answer.
Um...
Huh?
You dropped this.
Oh... When did I...
Thank you very much.
Well, what a coincidence!
But is it really a coincidence?
I just happened to be in the area.
I go to a cram school nearby.
Roger dodger.
Anyway, who were you just talking to?
That was a professor from my college.
I never expected you to catch me
getting trounced like that.
Ah... It must be exhausting having
a serious debate with a professor.
That's for sure.
But I know how to rejuvenate now and then
when I'm exhausted, so I'll be okay.
Rejuvenate?
Teasing you replenishes
the vigor in my heart, son.
Oh, thank you kindly for giving
me something to lean on!
Now hold on a second...
Stop Shoplifting!
It's a crime
Rewards Points Promotion
Earn up to 30%
Navigator
When You're Searching for a Book
I'm going shopping, so go on home without me
I don't expect anything from you,
so I don't want you to expect
anything from me either.
You mean Narasaka-san, right?
You two are friends?
We are. Although I think Maaya's
pretty much friends with everyone.
Mixed rice?
Oh, welcome home.
Thanks.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Oh, well...
You're always doing everything for me.
Is this okay for dinner?
Sure. You can warm it up in the microwave.
Okay. Got it.
Oh, wait.
Huh?
If you leave the lid on, it'll get all sticky.
Oh, no kidding.
Thanks, Ayase-san.
Want some coffee?
Huh?
Oh, sure.
Iced okay?
Yeah.
So, about the pool thing with Narasaka-san...
You're bringing that up again?
Yeah, well, I haven't gotten
the contact info I need yet.
She's probably still waiting
for a response from me.
Fine. I'll give it to you.
Ah, wait!
I don't actually care about her contact info.
I'm not doing this because
I want to go to the pool.
I want you to go to and have fun there.
I don't get it.
I mean, if I said I wanted to go,
I thought you might get jealous.
Me?
Yeah, you.
But why would I get jealous?
Well, don't you actually
want to go to the pool?
Sorry. Akiko-san told me a few things.
She said that ever since you were little,
you hated the heat and love the pool.
But that was when I was a kid.
Ayase-san...
Ayase-san, you always seem a little different
when you talk about Narasaka-san.
Like when we made sweet 'n' sour pork,
you looked really happy.
You had this glowing smile.
So I figured that if Narasaka-san
asked you to go to the pool,
you'd probably actually want to go.
I told you. I don't have the time.
Yeah, I know.
I have to study.
Right. I get that.
But you still need to find time to rel—
I can't relax!
This is why I worry about you.
If you keep pushing yourself like this,
sooner or later, you're gonna crash.
I know you want to hurry up
and become independent,
but you still have to make time to rest.
Ayase-san?
I'm going to go study.
Maaya
Tuesday, August 25th
Good morning, Ayase-san.
Good morning.
Did you not get to sleep?
I did.
At about six o'clock.
Six? You should try to sleep a bit more.
You don't have work until tonight.
I'll be fine. What time is it?
Oh, it's already that late?
I'm really sorry. There wasn't
anything for your dad to eat.
It's okay. He had some bread before he left.
I've never slept in this late before.
Probably the exhaustion catching up with you.
It's okay if you want to rest a little longer.
I'm really sorry.
I can make something for you right now.
Ayase-san.
Yes?
I want you to listen to me and not walk away.
About what?
About this.
When you moved in, do you
remember what you said to me?
When we decided to stop
talking formally to each other.
"It's a big help if we can
smooth things out this easily."
Yeah.
And right now, I can tell
how sleep-deprived you are.
I don't want to make you
cook for me in this state.
But it was all my idea to do the cooking.
Rules are one thing.
But in reality, things change.
Your mission today, Ayase-san,
is not to cook but to sleep.
B-But...
I wouldn't be saying this if you
were your normal self today.
But you know, you've never slept
in this late before. Isn't that right?
So these are unusual circumstances.
I'm just a little short on sleep.
That's reason enough.
You have a right to take a seat in this chair.
Come on.
Okay.
Think you can eat a piece of toast?
Yeah.
Should I grill the ham?
I do like it grilled.
You always brown it a bit, right?
That's the way I like it.
Me, too. It's better a little crispy.
Want some hot milk?
Huh?
But it's summer.
The air conditioning is on.
Also, if you're going back to sleep,
it might help to get a
warm drink inside you first.
I'll take one.
You got it.
Let's eat.
Here.
Oh, I forgot. Here's a spoon.
Thanks.
We should go to the pool.
Huh?
Really? That's great.
But there's one problem.
Huh?
You and I both have work that day.
Huh? What day is it?
Day after tomorrow.
Seriously?
Yeah, seriously.
But since you've decided to go,
let's make it happen.
Make it happen how?
We can trade shifts with other people.
Can we really do that?
Sure, no problem. It'll work out.
Aren't you hot? Are you okay?
I'm fine. The breeze helps.
Sorry about yesterday.
Huh?
After you came to work with Yomiuri-san,
I was kind of in a bad mood, wasn't I?
Um...
It's against the rules to hide it
when we feel uncomfortable, right?
It's okay. I'll be totally open with you.
If you two are going out,
I want you to come out and tell me.
We aren't going out.
Oh, you aren't?
Why did you think we were?
I don't know... Let's just leave it at that.
Listen, I think she's a really great person.
She's kind, considerate, beautiful,
and she has a good sense of humor.
Wait, why am I here promoting Yomiuri-san?
Huh? Uh...
If I say things like that,
it may influence you.
I should keep it to myself. Sorry.
You're forgiven.
But you really need to stop apologizing.
Okay. Got it.
Uh...
Why in the world did I bring my bike?
Huh?
I don't need it if we're walking together.
I figured you must've had some reason.
No, not at all. It was just out of habit.
Well, that happens sometimes.
Habits sure are hard to break.
Let's leave it at that.
It'll be fun.
Sunday, August 6th.
We're at the beach today.
It's really sunny. The breeze feels great.
Oh, Yuta! Don't run, okay?
Dad, look!
Hey, you found a bunch!
Look at this! I'm gonna give this one to Mom!
Oh, really? I bet that'll
make her really happy.
Yeah!
I really wanted her to come with us, though.
We'll come together another time.
Okay!
Oh! Next time, let's go to the pool!
Oh!
Episode 9 "Stepsister and Diary"
That does sound like fun.